Look at this.
What is this?
The icon in Tamil Nadu.
There is a
This must be a Ganesha's work.
Worked Paytm Payment
Dubai
Jalakala Jalakala Jalakala
Be Indian By Indian
There are many people like this.
It looks like a phone.
You are
making it difficult for the customers.
Why is it half closed?
Not laptop.
My face is jamming.
Hi Soldiers.
It looks
like a suitcase going to the village.
Bro bro bro
What bro?
You got the Jio book.
Tell me if it is good.
You have bought it yourself.
I know
that if I post a video about Jio book,
I will get views.
But,
For that,
If I get money for the rate of Jio book,
I won't get money.
But, that is not the main reason.
We have done a lot of Jio.
They have filed a case tomorrow.
We have to prove it.
As a customer, I will get views.
For that, this bill.
And this laptop.
Look at the bill.
Amazon bill.
So, I can ask questions now.
Because I am a customer.
Do you know what a customer is?
I don't know.
Have some respect.
So, this is the only thing.
Before this, there is Jio book 1.
This is Jio book 1.
This is Jio book 11.
After taking it, it was 11.
This Jio book 1 and Jio book 2.
For us, it is 2.
So, what is the difference between 2?
There is a difference in the box.
It is not the size.
What he did is nice.
Made in India in this place.
Made in China in this place.
Both are Chinese.
So, there is confusion.
What is the confusion?
Are you done?
Ok fine.
Now, let us open the box.
The bearded guy.
Uncle has posted a video.
He said that he has a beautiful laptop.
I think he has done this to help him.
He is the great master.
He has 20 million views.
Master is the best.
You are the only one in this area.
You are playing with others.
Jio book.
Look at the box.
They have given it in a recyclable cover.
Hey, I am here.
Where is the other laptop?
Give me the original laptop.
Look at the original laptop.
It looks like the old man's car.
Look at the laptop that is released now.
It is good.
If it was here, who would have done it?
I will take it to the shop.
Even the girl who
went to the king's court is catching me.
Let us see what else is in the box.
Look doctor.
Give me type C.
At least give me type B.
Poor guy.
Look, the same soldiers.
I thought.
You won't be there.
I think I will come back after 30 hours.
Ok.
Let us open the box.
Soldiers, this is the old one.
Keyboard is like this.
Key is being tracked.
The build quality is comparatively better.
The weight seems to be less.
Why is it less?
That is the reason.
Get started.
They have brought the keyboard edge to edge.
If they brought it here,
someone from China would have bought it.
Why did they bring it here?
Did they decide to give me a lesson?
There is no change in the OS.
It is the same OS.
Let us go with Chrome OS.
I think Chrome OS is open source.
Let us go with that.
What is this for?
Come here.
This is the store.
What is there in the store?
I think they have changed the store.
It is ok.
I will buy it for 14 rupees.
Why is it half closed?
You are dead.
He is not stuck with you.
You are stuck with him.
You are
manufacturing Mandarin Matrix in China.
I think a Chinese man has given you an app.
Welcome to Mandarin Matrix.
Chinese learning.
Your partner is Chinese learning.
Why should we learn Chinese?
Look here.
A Rambur company
is selling books for Chinese learning.
They are selling books for us.
I think
I will learn Hindi if I believe in them.
Why should they learn Chinese?
We can't
say anything if we use these software.
We can't accept what we say now.
We have to sudden it.
What is there inside?
I want to see that.
What are we going to do now?
We are going to see what is there inside.
But before that, we need to see something.
This video is sponsored.
I have come.
CDKeyoffer.com
CDKeyoffer
is a digital product key selling site.
Windows 10
Pro OM and MS office keys are very cheap.
If you use our promo code A2D,
you will get 30% off.
Don't forget to use the code.
Open it.
Okay.
It's open.
I think Renji has a screw in this.
Yes, soldiers.
He has a screw in this.
Look here.
What are you planning?
Thank you.
That's my product.
Soldiers,
last time we didn't have any cover sheet.
Look at this time.
They have kept it to spread heat.
This is for Jeeva.
Again, that China number is nice.
How the...
Okay, what kind of battery is this?
What kind of battery is this?
What is this?
We can't even do sales.
Battery.
This?
This won't work.
Let it be.
Let's open the original Jeeva book.
Oh, they have given a cover sheet in this.
They didn't give any infinix.
Last time we didn't have any cover sheet.
Sorry, I thought it was infinix.
It's okay, brother.
Okay, fine.
Both of them are...
It's like a chicken.
Let's see what's the difference.
This is Jeeva Book 1.
This is Jeeva Book 2.
The first thing is the battery.
The battery is 5000 mAh.
In this case, it's only 4000 mAh.
They reduced it to 1500 mAh.
That's why they reduced the weight.
Because the mAh has been reduced.
There is a battery connector here.
We have to remove the battery.
We have to do that all the time.
We have to do it here.
Battery.
Kit Kat printer.
Shenzhen utility.
Energy.
This is the manufacturer.
This is Jeeva Book 1's battery.
It has a noise.
Don't talk in a bad way.
Okay, soldiers.
Now remove...
Motherboard.
Jeeva Book 1's neural schema.
That's the motherboard.
Soldiers.
This is the neural schema.
I have removed the brain separately.
One is Jeeva New.
This is Jeeva Old.
It looks like a phone.
Who is talking?
Ganesha.
Okay, soldiers.
This is Jeeva Book 2's motherboard.
Do you have this?
This is the media tech.
8788B.
And this is Micron's 4GP RAM.
I think it is LPDDR4.
This is Kingston's memory 600GP.
It is not memory.
It is EMMC.
EMMC.
600GP.
Do you see it?
I have put it there.
And this side...
This is Jeeva Book 1.
There will be two chips in this.
Because...
This is Qualcomm's Snapdragon 665.
And this is Samsung's memory plus NAND.
EMMC.
Not NAND.
So both are together.
Okay, soldiers.
And I found another important thing.
So this looks like USB 3.0.
But actually...
It is connected with 4 pins.
Do you see it?
This is actually USB 2.0.
Similarly, if you look at this...
It looks like 3.0.
But if you look at the back...
It is 2.0.
This is cheating.
Hey, what is this crap?
Okay, soldiers.
Both are separated.
Now I will add one and see how it is.
And see if there is any improvement.
Two weeks later.
Soldiers.
This is the usage date.
There are many important videos.
That is, why did they release Jeeva Book?
Look at this.
Actually, what is Jeeva Book for?
Learning Book.
For small children.
If you come to Corona lockdown...
We have to shut down our home.
That's why this is there.
And then...
In the ad...
A cook is doing this.
You
can watch the video on YouTube and learn.
To learn.
Who will learn?
Kids will learn.
They go to school.
They will learn.
They have laptops.
But the problem is...
This is an app store.
That is, Jeeva Store name.
There are three categories,
features and additional apps.
If you go to the additional apps...
There are many apps.
Good thing, right?
Good thing.
But there is a problem in it.
First thing is banned apps.
Look at that.
By the Indian government...
That is, by the central government...
All banned Chinese apps are in this.
Hey, you fool.
The first app is TikTok.
Tiktok banned app.
But it is in this.
TikTok music videos and live.
TikTok works.
What is this?
TikTok
is still being used by some community.
You think
you are buying a Jeeva book and using it.
I have a doubt on you.
Are you listening to me?
Why are you speaking in Tamil?
This is a food for soldiers.
Why is he tracking me?
Hey, come.
I am coming.
Food for soldiers?
If you want soldiers,
put it in the comments.
Tell me if you want.
Did you see, soldiers?
The government banned Chinese apps.
Jeeva book is the cheapest Indian laptop.
Did you poke your face?
If you are
worried about the ban of TikTok videos...
Buy this Jeeva book.
I have the second one.
If you want, you can ping me.
If you ask me about this...
There is an app called X.
You know it and it is called Twitter.
But if you buy it below...
Look at this.
What is this?
If I had seen this, I would have blurred it.
There will only be a hub.
You can find the rest.
Bro, the ban is in India.
It doesn't work like that.
Look above that.
Tarubo VPN.
I have given it nearby.
Look here, soldiers.
I have installed it.
It is coming.
It is so bad.
It is
coming differently than what I thought.
What is this?
If you see someone inside, he is removing
the dowsers and is standing like a god.
If you ask me if this is the only thing...
What is there?
Look here.
X videos, movie, P***.
Hardcore P*** videos are free.
What is free?
Look here.
Tamil is bad.
The verb for Maache LOL.
I can only see ads in Telangana as we're
selling the icon are used for children.
Even the icon in appears
on many wee ingredients names as well.
You'll sink your tongue.
Look here soldiers.
Mixed Text reading ad...
Yeah, I bought this tissue & sipped my tea.
Look at the different of this area.
This isn't world.
One dot, two dots, three dots.
Its a styled защet spot.
Holy shit.
sh Jesse Lockwood is annoying.
This is what the Jio gave.
So we give cutting and cutting?
Do you know how bad this is?
Look here, there's a chandelier.
Erection problem.
Hey Tommy, get up.
Soldiers, this is not only for age landing.
It's not normal landing.
There's a doctor at 11 in the night.
They've advertised this as wrong.
Not for kids.
Only for...
Okay fine.
This is bad.
What is this?
This is the map in the Jio book.
So if you ask if it's not in Jio book 1.
They released it.
They've put it in a box.
There's no software update for this.
The Jio OS in this is 0.1.
The one in this is 1.0.
You killed me.
Red chip, blue color laptop.
This is a serious problem.
Why I'm saying this.
We won't buy this.
Why?
Because
most of the people who watch our videos.
They don't buy it.
But they watch TV.
They have a chance to buy this.
Whatever it may be.
The sales may be low.
But it's not like that in North.
They've bought it with their money.
For example.
Our uncle.
He posted
a video saying this laptop is not good.
But now.
He posted
a video saying this laptop is super.
Another thing is.
It works with Ctrl C and Ctrl V.
It's an additional feature.
If you connect your phone to USB or OTG.
It works with Ctrl V and Ctrl C.
It's a basic thing.
It's an additional feature.
He's also saying this.
He has also posted this.
Worst behavior.
So even on days like this.
Not only that.
People there.
If you say that it's an Indian made product.
Many people have the
mindset to buy it with their eyes closed.
For example.
Lenovo took me to Delhi for an event.
They have launched
the workstation and servers there.
Everyone who came there asked questions.
I also asked questions to that person.
You must have seen the video.
IPM is there.
But there is a guy from the north.
He asked me.
They banned the import of laptops.
You manufacture it in India.
Where do you manufacture it?
He said.
It's not wrong to ask this.
But it's wrong to ask anyone.
Because Lenovo is a Chinese company.
A Chinese company
is running an event in a hotel room.
When asked to manufacture it in India.
What will he do?
Not like that.
Like this.
He said.
He managed and sent it.
The reason I'm saying this.
See how much they are involved in it.
They are like that.
They will definitely buy it.
In the north.
The people support the idea of Indian-made.
They think
it's our basic duty to support them.
For example.
You have two pills.
Red pill and blue pill.
Red pill is Chinese-made.
Even if the Chinese-made is better.
Even if it is cheap.
They will buy the blue pill.
Indian-made.
There are
many people who say be Indian by Indian.
You are anti-India.
Their target ends there.
There is no need to come here.
There is a matter.
Their village doesn't have a mother laptop.
That's why it exists.
Only if you use your mother's laptop.
You will know.
There is no such laptop.
Since there is no mother laptop.
Everyone is saying this is okay.
But if you give your mother's laptop.
It will be great.
At least change the name.
It will be good if you give it.
In this.
There is no Google play service.
They use their own.
We know that Android is open source.
We have said in the previous video.
But Android's play services are open source.
There is no Android play service.
There is Google play service.
There is Google play.
It is not free.
Why should we give money?
We have bare Android.
We can use it.
They did this.
Not only that.
We developed apps for that.
We went to the app developers.
They brought our app to the app store.
Instead of that.
They have already.
There is an app on online.
There is a website.
They tie up with that.
They integrated inside.
The problem with integrating.
They have a Gilme app.
They have added that app.
The problem with whom?
Only with Jio.
Jio should have filtered this.
Instead of filtering.
It is not a good thing.
Look at the top.
Disclaimer.
The additional
apps are not hosted on Jio store.
And it is being
made available through that party store.
Jio doesn't take any
responsibility or liability for the app.
He will bomb it.
He will take it.
It is like that.
Who is the one who puts that party inside?
Jio only.
Because we download it in Jio store.
Sometimes they take responsibility.
Others don't take responsibility.
I can't take responsibility for this.
Because that party.
Who is that party?
They didn't put their name.
Who should I ask?
Jio should be asked.
Because the product is Jio.
The software is Jio.
The shop is also Jio.
Jio is being kept in the digital store.
Even the Sim is Jio.
So when all are Jio.
If the store is that party.
If the app is that party.
They won't accept it.
So Jio should take responsibility for this.
And remove all this.
If Jio takes responsibility.
The laptop should also be destroyed.
I am telling the truth.
It is not available in search.
It will come when you scroll.
I will show you when I scroll.
It will open when you click.
So it is not a good thing.
Outside only.
School, student, etc.
But there is no problem with that.
Look here.
Ashing include standard io.h.
stdio.h.
After that there is no space.
There is nothing.
Look at the int main.
If you give like this.
It will be syntax error.
If you put this.
It will be error.
Editor.
Put it in the online company and show.
Does it error?
So in the ad.
They are showing you with small boys.
But this is an app for small boys.
No.
It is not.
It is a good thing.
None of our Tamil creators.
Sponsored this video.
That is great.
Because I think it will work.
The problem for us is.
If we do in Tamil.
Our videos will not be seen in North.
That is why.
I think
it is better if we put Hindi subtitles.
Look at the audience.
First put English subtitles.
Soldiers.
It is difficult to put English subtitles.
No one is coming.
If you know.
Tell me anything.
It is said to be done at a low price.
They ask for a lot of money.
Because they
ask for 1000 to 200 rupees for a video.
It is very difficult.
Content.
If you want to come to the content.
Put it in the A2D Media Group.
If you want to edit the subtitles.
You can join here.
Okay soldiers.
This is it.
Those who have seen this video.
There are many things.
Like internal or hardware.
But.
There is nothing to talk about.
Let's say it simply.
Simply yes.
No need to buy.
You don't have to buy.
After watching the old video.
You know why I bought it.
Because this is.
Laptop bill.
My moon is jamming.
I will show you that I have a bill.
That is why.
That is why I bought it.
You don't think wrong.
Why?
Money.
You are wasting money.
This is my moon jamming.
Take care.
That is why.
I am a customer.
I should not trouble the customer.
Okay.
So.
Next.
Make a good product from the next product.
I will give a good review.
Okay.
Fine.
Okay soldiers.
I will see you in the next video.
Before that.
Follow me.
Instagram is there.
If you have cheated like this.
Put it in the comment section below.
Your opinion is right.
Put it in the comments.
And most importantly.
Share it with others.
Because only then.
You will get more awareness.
And more digital products.
They call it digital literacy.
In our country.
There is a new word.
I will add that word.
Add the word digital literacy.
That is when.
Digital literacy will grow.
This awareness will grow.
Okay.
Bye.